1and may containmature subject matter.
可能包含成熟的主题。
Viewer discretionis advised.
建议观众自由选择。
aAll singing:inBoob world, boob world.
所有歌唱：书中世界，书中世界。
It's a world for you,but it's actually two.
对你来说这是一个世界，但实际上是两个。
Boob World!
胸部世界！
I gotta say, Morty, it's weirdthat you wanted me to come,
我得说，莫蒂，你想让我来真奇怪，
but I'm actuallyexstyched about it --
但我真的很高兴--
that's excited, stoked,and psyched.
很兴奋，很兴奋，很兴奋。
I didn't want you to come.Talk to Rick.
我不想你来。跟瑞克谈谈。
Truth is, Summer, Boob World'sbeen at the center
事实是，夏天，胸部是世界的中心
of a few protests every dayfor 30 years,
30年来每天都有一些抗议活动，
so they've recently rebranded asa boob empowerment experience,
所以他们最近重新命名了asa的胸部授权体验，
and if we bring a female,we get in for free.
如果我们带一个女人，我们就可以免费进去。
So, I'm, like, what, a Coke canyou're taking to Six Flags?
所以，我，就像，什么，一个可乐罐你要带到六旗？
No, 'cause once youget into Six Flags,
不，因为一旦你进入六旗，
you can throwyour Coke can away.
你可以扔掉你的可乐罐。
No fucking way.
他妈的不行。
It can't be.
不可能。
Holy shit, holy shit, holy shit.Oh, look at that.
天哪，天哪，天哪。哦，看那个。
-What is it?-It's a GoTron ferret.
-它是什么？-它是一只哥德伦雪貂。
It's not a GoTron ferret,Morty.
这不是哥德伦雪貂，莫蒂。
It's the blueGoTron ferret.
是蓝哥特龙雪貂。
Boob World is canceled.No, Rick, no.
胸部世界取消了。不，瑞克，不。
You promised.You always do this.
你答应过的。你总是这样。
Tell you what, Morty,I'll let you choose.
告诉你吧，莫蒂，我让你选择。
Do you really thinkBoob World -
你真的认为胸部世界-
Yes.Let me finish.
好的。让我说完。
Is more important --Yes.
更重要的是——是的。
Let me finish!Than have all five
让我说完！比五个都好
of the only five GoTron ferretsin the universe?
宇宙中仅有的五只哥德伦雪貂？
Are you finished?Yes. So, let's go.
你说完了吗？是的。所以，我们走吧。
Summer, help me hook the winchup to the ferret.
夏天，帮我把温丘普钩到雪貂身上。
Sure.What the hell?!
当然。怎么了？！
You said you wereletting me choose.
你说你让我选择。
Yeah, whether to breakmy fucking heart.
是啊，是不是该伤我的心。
You chose badly.
你选错了。
Morty:That's how it all began.
莫蒂：事情就是这样开始的。
To my sister,it was just another game.
对我妹妹来说，这只是另一场游戏。
But what shedidn't know --
但她不知道的是--
Summer: That was the momenteverything changed.
萨默：一切都改变了。
Morty:Wait. What?
莫蒂：等等。什么？
I had gotten my first taste ofrespect and my first voiceover.
我第一次尝到了尊重的滋味，第一次画外音。
I can hear you.Can you hear me?
我听得见。你听得见吗？
And I knew then and thereI wanted more of both.
我当时就知道我想要两样东西。
Hello?
你好？
Beth, Jerry,do something fun with us.
贝丝，杰瑞，和我们一起做点有趣的事。
A giant monster is attackingin the Nibblenug system.
一个巨大的怪物正在攻击Nibblenug系统。
Your suitsare in the bathroom.
你的手提箱在浴室里。
Mine smells skeletony.
我的闻起来像骷髅。
I have a chiropractorappointment.
我有脊椎指压疗法。
What are youinvolving us in?
你让我们卷入了什么？
Rick's been collectingGoTron ferrets,
里克一直在收集哥德伦雪貂，
and now that he has all five,we can combine them into --
现在他有了所有的五个，我们可以把它们结合起来--
Morty, for Christ's sakespoilers.
莫蒂，看在上帝的份上。
Spoilers, Morty.
破坏者，莫蒂。
WE don't needto sell this to anyone.
我们不需要把这个卖给任何人。
There's a giantmonster attacking.
有一个巨大的怪物正在进攻。
In the Nibblenug system.
在Nibblenug系统中。
Since when does this housecare about alien lives.
这房子什么时候开始关心外星生命了。
We don't even watchBritish television.
我们甚至不看英国电视。
Told you. Let's just getGene from next door
告诉你了。我们去隔壁找吉恩吧
and a homeless guy.No. Hold on.
一个无家可归的人。不。等等。
Fuck Gene.Fuck the homeless.
去他妈的吉恩去他妈的流浪汉。
Your kids and their grandpaare asking you to do
你的孩子和他们的祖父母要求你这么做
an activity with them.
和他们一起的活动。
When did that stop beinga parent's wettest dream?
那是什么时候停止做父母最湿的梦的？
I guess around the timeour family created
我猜在我们家创造
a giant incest baby,and the government
一个巨大的乱伦婴儿和政府
launched it into space.
把它发射到太空。
Oh my God, we made a giantincest baby.
天哪，我们生了个大宝宝。
Oh my God,you might be a clone.
天哪，你可能是克隆人。
I exist because you guysfailed to abort me.
我的存在是因为你们没能把我打掉。
We get the family we get,not the one we want.
我们有自己的家庭，而不是我们想要的。
And if you want to keepthe one you got,
如果你想保留你的那个，
get your asses intosome anime spacesuits.
快穿上动漫宇航服。
-Fair enough.-Okay.
-很公平。-好的。
Good work, Summer Camp.Yeah.
干得好，夏令营。是的。
I'm exci-tokedabout this.
我很高兴知道这件事。
Sure you are -- now.
当然——现在。
Morty:Something new was forming,and I was at the bottom of it.
莫蒂：一些新的东西正在形成，而我在它的底部。
Summer:I let Morty have his voiceover.It's really all he had left.
萨默：我把他的画外音给莫蒂了。他只剩下这些了。
Okay, can you hear meor not?
好吧，你能听见我说话吗？
Do you mean can I, Summer,hear you?
你的意思是我，萨默，能听见吗？
No. My voiceovercan hear your voiceover.
不，我的配音听不到你的配音。
What's the difference?
有什么区别？
One would be telepathy,dumbass.
一个是心灵感应，笨蛋。
Now what?
现在怎么办？
Now, we --
现在，我们--
All:Go, Team GoTron!
全体：加油，哥德伦队！
Where are we zip-lining throughfuturistic metallic tunnels to?
我们要用拉链把金属隧道拉到哪里去？
Each robot ferret is at adifferent location on Earth.
每只机器雪貂在地球上的不同位置。
You're going to the centerof a volcano.
你要去火山中心。
Thank you?
非常感谢。
Okay, well,this isn't not fun.
好吧，这可不好玩。
Regroup on me.
重新集结在我身上。
I'll shoot a portalto Nibblenug.
我要射一个小牛。
Did I just monorailfrom my kitchen to Hawaii
我刚从厨房单轨到夏威夷吗
just to regroup in outer spaceabove my kitchen?
就为了在我厨房上方的外层空间重新集合？
Uh, Summer?It's cool, Dad. Shut up.
呃，夏天？很酷，爸爸。闭嘴。
Everybody,attack one at a time!
所有人，一次攻击一个！
Is thatthe best way to --
那是最好的方法吗--
Tee up something awesome?Yes. Follow me.
有什么很棒的吗？是的。跟着我。
Guys, we did our best,but there's only one hope.
伙计们，我们已经尽力了，但只有一个希望。
Activating link-dock.
激活链接驳接。
Inter-Morphs -- rad-ified.PostiTrinos -- maximized.
互变形——rad-ified.positrinos——最大化。
Holy shit, I-I can't believethis is working.
妈的，我真不敢相信这能奏效。
Go, go, team!It's GoTron time!
加油，加油，队员们！哥德伦时间到了！
Oh, my God.Hell yes!
哦，我的天哪。是的！
This is amazing!
太棒了！
Okay, now we canknock it around a little bit,
好吧，现在我们可以稍微改变一下，
but trust me, we're stillbuilding to something.
但相信我，我们还在努力。
How do we --Just hit buttons.
我们该怎么做——只要按一下按钮。
we're too big to fail.
我们太大了，不能失败。
I kicked him!That was me, right?
我踢了他！是我，对吧？
Morty: Uppercut!
莫蒂：上勾！
I can't believe I almostwent to the chiropractor!
我简直不敢相信我居然去看了按摩师！
I've been waitinga long time for this.
我已经等了很久了。
Form Luminous Energy Sword!
形成光能剑！
That's your ass,Mamma Jamma.
那是你的屁股，妈妈。
Morty: These werethe good times,
莫蒂：这些都是好时光，
when we felt likewe could do anything.
当我们觉得我们可以做任何事的时候。
But anythingis never quite everything.
但任何事情都不是全部。
And pretty soon...
很快。。。
That was nothing -- nothingcompared to what we can do.
和我们能做的相比，这算不了什么。
There are infinite universeswhere I still don't haveall five ferrets.
在无限的宇宙里，我还没有拥有所有的五只雪貂。
Th-th-those versions of mewould do anything
那些版本的我可以做任何事
to completetheir collections.
完成他们的收藏。
Okay, but Rick, remember whatyou told me to remind you?
好吧，但是瑞克，还记得你告诉我要提醒你什么吗？
Sometimes, enough is...
有时候，够了。。。
Sometimes,enough is enough.
有时候，够了就够了。
Morty, what are you doing?
莫蒂，你在干什么？
He gets obsessed, Summer -
他被迷住了，Summer-
When are you goingto find your shame?
你什么时候才能找到你的耻辱？
I have more.Grandpa just gave
我还有。爷爷刚刚给了我
everybody the high pointof their lives,
每个人都在生命的巅峰，
and before he did,every single one of you
在他之前，你们每个人
was trying to talk himout of it.
试图说服他放弃。
Wait. Yeah.Wha-wha-what the fuck!
等待。是啊。他妈的！
Now, he says we can go higher,and big surprise,
现在，他说我们可以走得更高，让人大吃一惊，
it's time todrag him down again.
又到了教训他的时候了。
Well, I vote --No voting.
我投反对票。
No debate.It's not a democracy.
不用辩论，这不是民主。
It's a Rickpublic.You're in or you're out.
这是一个公共场所。你要么进去，要么出去。
Obviously, I'm in.I never said I wasn't in.
很明显，我参加了。我从没说过我不参加。
Me, neither.Tell us what we're doing next.
我也是。告诉我们下一步要做什么。
Uh, I want to put togethera cookout.
呃，我想一起去野餐。
That's it? I was honestlyprepared to blow someone.
就这样？我真的准备炸死一个人。
-Jerry.-I said "prepared"and "someone."
-杰瑞。-我说“准备好了”和“有人”
Morty: Rick invited fiveversions of our family
莫蒂：里克邀请了我们家五个版本的人
from different universes,each with incomplete GoTrons.
来自不同的宇宙，每一个都有不完整的哥特伦。
I didn't have anyoneto talk to,
我没人说话，
since the other four Mortyshad been to Boob World.
因为其他四个死者都去过胸部世界。
Did you walkon the beach?
你在海滩上散步吗？
The beach that's all boobs?
海滩都是胸部？
No, the beachthat's all sand.
不，海滩全是沙子。
Yes, the boob one!
是的，胸部那个！
Rick was in the garage with theheads of the five families.
里克和五户人家的户主在车库里。
Ugh, and Summer.
啊，还有夏天。
Summer:In that first sit-down,
萨默：第一次坐下来，
it was Big Fat Rick,
是大胖子里克，
Ricardo Montaya,Hot Head Rick --
里卡多·蒙塔亚，头脑发热的瑞克--
he got that name because he wasprone to dramatic outbursts -
他之所以叫这个名字，是因为他很容易激动-
and Lil' Ricky Wrap-it-Up,
小瑞奇把它包起来，
who was always greatat the end of a meeting.
他总是在会议结束时表现出色。
At the head of it all,me and Grandpa Rick.
最重要的是，我和瑞克爷爷。
Now, don't getme wrong, C137,
别误会，C137，
we're happyfor your good fortune.
我们为你的好运感到高兴。
But we did nottravel to your universe
但我们没有去你们的宇宙旅行
just to have it rubbedin our faces.
只是为了让它在我们脸上摩擦。
Come on, Big Fat Rick,you know your face
来吧，大胖子里克，你知道你的脸
is too smallto rub anything on.
太小了，擦不到任何东西。
My face is the same sizeas yours.
我的脸和你的一样大。
Wow. Huh. Hold on.
哇！呵呵。等等。
I'll be damned.
我会被诅咒的。
You're so fatyou're an optical illusion.
你太胖了，简直是幻觉。
Summer, give 'em the pitch.
Summer，给他们机会。
We're offering to helpeach of your families
我们愿意帮助你们每个家庭
complete theirfull GoTrons.
完成他们的全部哥特龙。
In exchangefor some concessions.
作为让步的交换。
Ever since I was a little boyin the slums,
从我还是个小男孩的时候就在贫民窟里，
I have dreamed of havinga complete GoTron.
我梦想拥有一个完整的哥德伦。
But concessions?
但是让步呢？
I hope you meanthe kind from a counter.
我希望你是指柜台上的那种。
I hope she meansice cream!
我希望她是指奶油！
We'd like youto relocate your families
我们希望你重新安置你的家人
to this universe,and let me make some
为了这个宇宙，让我做一些
modificationsto the GoTrons --
对哥特人的改造--
in the interest of usall working together.
为了我们大家的共同努力。
Want to knowwhat I think?
想知道我怎么想吗？
Sure, Hothead Rick, just don'tunexpectedly fly off the handle.
当然，暴躁的瑞克，别想当然地发火。
I think you guysgot a lot of nerveacting better than us!
我觉得你们比我们紧张多了！
This is the family that madea giant incest baby!
这就是玛迪亚家族那个巨大的乱伦婴儿！
Had the governmentlaunch it into space!
让政府把它送上太空！
It's still floatin' aroundout there somewhere!
它还在某处飘浮！
Are we ever gonnalive that down?
我们能把它记下来吗？
If I get a full GoTron,it won't be by kissing your ass,
如果我得到一个完整的哥特伦，它不会通过亲吻你的屁股，
it'll be by takingwhat's mine -- yours!
我要拿走我的——你的！
Hey! Gross!No need.
嘿！恶心！不需要。
And you were driving...a ferret?
你开着…雪貂？
We all are, moron!Give me key!
我们都是，白痴！把钥匙给我！
You'll regret this,you level-headed fucks.
你会后悔的，你们这些头脑冷静的混蛋。
Obviously, we predictedthat might happen,
显然，我们已经预料到了，
which is why we haveYo-Yo Rick on standby.
所以我们让Yo-Yo Rick待命。
Anybody got beefwith Yo-Yo?
有人和溜溜球在一起吗？
Some people think he's lame,but to me,
有些人认为他是瘸子，但对我来说，
he's lame in a cool waybecause he owns it.
他很酷，因为他拥有它。
Cool. That concludes business.Lil' Ricky Wrap it Up?
很酷。生意到此结束了。小瑞奇结束了吗？
Raise 'em up, boys!Oh-pah!
举起手来，孩子们！哦，呸！
Summer: And so, we helpedour people find their ferrets.
萨默：所以，我们帮助我们的人找到他们的雪貂。
How they got them,not our problem.
他们怎么得到的，不是我们的问题。
Then, we got downto business.
然后，我们开始谈正事。
Here's how it worked --
下面是它的工作原理--
if a giant monsterattacked your planet,
如果一个巨大的怪物袭击了你的星球，
we all got the alert.
我们都收到警报了。
Man:♪ Hey, hey, mama mia's ♪
男：♪ 嘿，嘿，米娅妈妈♪
♪ Got a plate of spaghettifor the takin' ♪
♪ 给羚羊准备了一盘意大利面条♪
♪ Papa pia's got a great bigrobot that he's makin' ♪
♪ 皮亚爸爸有个很棒的大机器人♪
♪ I got the moonin both my eyes ♪
♪ 我两眼都有月亮♪
♪ You got a bowl of pizza pie,hey! ♪
♪ 你有一碗比萨饼，嘿！♪
♪ A bit of pasta with some animecombined, yeah ♪
♪ 一点意大利面和一些动物组合，是吗♪
We formedfive GoTrons.
我们组成了五个哥特人。
And those GoTronsformed the GoGoTron.
那些哥德伦形成了戈戈戈特伦。
All: Go, GoGoTron!
全体：加油，戈戈特伦！
Man:♪ Take it away, boys! ♪
男：♪ 把它拿走，孩子们！♪
Rick: I will neverget sick of this!
里克：我永远不会厌倦这个！
If you were a giant monsterat that time, in our universe,
如果你当时是个巨大的怪物，在我们的宇宙里，
you never had a chance.
你从来没有机会。
Man: ♪ A bit of pastawith some anime combined ♪
男：♪ 一点意大利面和一些动漫结合在一起♪
♪ 'Cause we're two genres, buteach one is intertwined, yeah ♪
♪ '因为我们是两个流派，但每一个都是交织在一起的，是吗♪
Mine needs a weaponlike a Yo-Yo.
我的需要像溜溜球一样的武器。
And a Yo-Yo on the chest.Are you listening to me?
胸前还有个溜溜球。你在听我说吗？
I-I need you to respectthis partnership.
我-我需要你尊重我们的合作关系。
I kept Rick removedfrom the ugly stuff.
我让里克远离那些丑陋的东西。
If you got in his way,I got you out of the way.
如果你挡了他的路，我就把你挡开。
And that made more roomto move up.
这样就有了更大的空间。
The head of my right arm.
我右臂的头。
Morty: Me? I ended up the leftfoot of the left foot --
莫蒂：我？我最后是左脚的左脚--
I guess because our robotdidn't have an asshole.
我猜是因为我们的机器人没有混蛋。
Summer:Well, it had one.
萨默：嗯，它有一个。
Bitch! When are you gonnastop breaking my balls?
婊子！你什么时候能阻止我？
You win, okay?
你赢了，好吗？
We're not competing, Morty.And there's your answer.
我们没有竞争，莫蒂。这是你的答案。
I could move you up if I couldtrust you to put family first.
如果我相信你能把家庭放在第一位，我可以把你提升。
H-how is thatputting family first?
怎么把家庭放在第一位？
Show me all the blueprints!Show me all the blueprints!
给我看看所有的蓝图！给我看看所有的蓝图！
I agree.That's an issue.
我同意。这是个问题。
Big Fat Rick, his flask staysfull or your locker gets empty.Thanks.
大胖子里克，他的瓶子满了，否则你的储物柜就空了。谢谢。
I know it feels goodwhen he likes you,
我知道当他喜欢你的时候感觉很好，
but that doesn't meanhim liking you makes you good.
但这并不意味着他喜欢你会让你变好。
Solid babble, Morty -- like afortune cookie written by Borat.
牢不可破的胡言乱语，莫蒂——就像波拉特写的一块甜饼。
Yeah, I'm notas smart as you.
是的，我没有你聪明。
That's why I knowyou know what I mean.
所以我知道你知道我的意思。
You mean, if I reallyloved my family,
你是说，如果我真的爱我的家人，
I'd give control of it backto your jealous ass.
我会把控制权还给你嫉妒的屁股。
Green Ferret Four needs a wash,and we're out of detergent.
绿雪貂四号需要洗一洗，我们的洗涤剂用完了。
I just bought a box.
我刚买了一盒。
And Grandpa snorted it becauseyou make him feel fenced in.
爷爷吸鼻涕是因为你让他觉得被束缚住了。
Rick: Sum-Sum?
里克：求和？
Get two boxes.
拿两个盒子。
one of the planets we saved,
我们拯救的行星之一，
and built a secret nightclubon it,
在那里建了一个秘密夜总会，
a place no enemiescould find us --
一个没有敌人能找到我们的地方--
unless you countmy brother.
除非你把我哥哥算在内。
Morty: I didn't even havemy own ferret anymore.
莫蒂：我连自己的雪貂都没有了。
Summer made mesomething called
夏天制造了一种叫做
an "associatesecurity chief" --
一个“联合安全负责人”--
whatever the hellthat means.
不管那是什么意思。
Rick:Look at this guy.
里克：看看这家伙。
And look at this guy.Look-look at this guy over here.
看看这家伙。看看这家伙。
Oh, there she is!My Baby Princess!
哦，她来了！我的小公主！
Get up here.Stop the music.
站起来，停止音乐。
This. Is. Our. Queef --O-our Queen.
这个。是。我们的。女王——我们的女王。
She saved my life.She-she set me free.
她救了我的命。她让我自由了。
We wouldn't have what we havewithout this crazy bitch.
如果没有这个疯狂的婊子，我们就不会拥有我们所拥有的。
And she's gota special announcement.
她得到了一个特别的通知。
Summer, tell 'em wha-whatwe talked about.
Summer，告诉他们我们谈了什么。
Now? I don't think --
现在？我不认为--
Okay, I'll do it.God damn.
好吧，我会的。该死的。
Morty: The new jobdid have some perks --
莫蒂：新工作确实有一些额外津贴--
like, I got to be aroundthe night Summer realized
比如说，我得在夏天意识到
she was inover her head.
她在她的头上。
Okay, I've got 90 extra ferrets,which means I need 10 more,
好吧，我还有90只雪貂，也就是说我还需要10只，
and then four of youget your own GoGoTron,
然后你们四个人有了自己的GoGoTron，
and 20%of youget a GoTron,
20%的人有个哥德伦，
'cause we're all gonna havea fucking GoGoGoTron.
因为我们都会有一个该死的GoGoGoTron。
He's very excited.Um...
他很兴奋。嗯。。。
Oh-pah!
哦，呸！
I hate my family.
我讨厌我的家人。
You should.
你应该。
Get in.
当选。
How's it going withyour grandpa's compulsiveness?
你爷爷的强迫症怎么样了？
Is your sisterstill enabling it? Huh?
你的姐妹们还没启用吗？嗯？
Who are you people?
你们是谁？
Let's just say we'rethe rightful ownersof these ferrets.
就说我们是这些雪貂的合法主人吧。
Then, why were they scattered,and buried across the universe?
那么，它们为什么分散在宇宙中呢？
We mean in a more general,cultural sense. Arrrgh!
我们的意思是在更普遍的文化意义上。啊！
What your Grandpa didis called "appropriation."
你爷爷所做的被称为“拨款”
Not cool!Hunnnnngh!
不酷！亨恩！
Look, Morty,we've been watching.
听着，莫蒂，我们一直在看。
We know you're the onethat knows what's best.
我们知道你知道什么是最好的。
Work with usfrom the inside.
从内部与我们合作。
Help us take overthis operation.
帮我们做这个手术。
We're literally designed for it.Mm-hmmmmmm!
我们真的是为它而设计的！
Nobody will knowit was you.
没人会知道是你干的。
Then, you can get backto what's important.
然后，你就可以回到重要的事情上。
Are those Boob Bucks?
那些是胸块吗？
Legal tender at every kioskand ride! Huuunh!
合法货币在每一个亭骑！呼恩！
I can't.
我不能。
Summer's treating me like shit,but she's still my sister.
Summer把我当屎一样对待，但她还是我妹妹。
That's really noble, Morty.
真是高尚，莫蒂。
If you were in our family,your loyalty would be rewarded.
如果你在我们家，你的忠诚会得到回报。
But you're not in our family,which means we can kill you.
但你不在我们家，这意味着我们可以杀了你。
Oh, yeah?
哦，是吗？
Morty: And sure enough,just when I stuck my neck out
莫蒂：果然，就在我伸出脖子的时候
for the family,it got stomped on anyway.
对这个家庭来说，不管怎么说，都是被践踏了。
-Dad!-Mom! Dad!
-爸爸-妈妈！爸爸！
Hothead Rick, baby!
暴躁的瑞克，宝贝！
I set myselfup for that!
我自己准备的！
-What the hell happened?!-Hothead Rick.
-到底发生了什么-暴躁的瑞克。
How did he getso close to us?
他怎么离我们这么近？
Morty was supposedto be security!
莫蒂应该是保安！
-Morty?-I-I-I stepped away, alright?
-莫蒂？-我-我-我走开了，好吗？
But-but not tolet that happen!
但不是为了让它发生！
Morty, we're notattractive strangers
莫蒂，我们不是有吸引力的陌生人
next to youon a flight to Paris,
在飞往巴黎的航班上，你旁边，
traveling aloneto get over a breakup,
独自旅行来克服分手，
so this is no timeto be coy!
所以现在不是害羞的时候！
-Oh...pah.-Lil' Ricky.
-哦…呸。-小瑞奇。
I'm all wrapped up,Summer.
我都准备好了，夏天。
Guys, I know you don't trust me,but what have we become?
伙计们，我知道你们不信任我，但我们变成什么样了？
Why are wedoing this anymore?
我们为什么还要这样？
Because it's fun,you little rat.
因为这很有趣，你这个小老鼠。
Now go home,and play video games
现在回家玩电子游戏
while we clean upthese bodies,
当我们清理尸体的时候，
or your mother and I will hirepeople to break your knees!
否则你妈妈和我会雇人打断你的膝盖！
This is $16,000we got from the deep state
这是我们从深州得到的16000美元
for stepping onthat trailer park.
在拖车停车场踩踏。
That should be enough for schoollunch and home repairs.
这应该足够学校午餐和家庭维修了。
Now, I gottaturn my back on you.
现在，我背对着你。
No!
不！
Summer:With Morty out of the way,things were looking up.
萨默：莫蒂不碍事了，情况好转了。
But looksaren't everything.
但不是所有的。
Hi, Summer. Um, my cockpit'snot getting Wi-Fi.
嗨，Summer。嗯，我的驾驶舱没有无线网络。
Dad, you know that's notwhat I do around here.
爸爸，你知道我在这可不是干这个的。
Oh, I'm not your Dad.I'm a version of him.
哦，我不是你爸爸。我是他的一个版本。
This is my first day here,
这是我来这里的第一天，
and I-I'm not surewhat you do around here.
我不知道你在这干什么。
Then fuck off.Oh, fuck you.
那就滚开。哦，去你妈的。
Excuse me?I want your ID.
什么？我要你的身份证。
Mom. Are you Mom? Can youcontrol your rookie Jerrys.
妈妈。你是妈妈吗？你能控制你的菜鸟杰瑞吗。
Sweetie, we're alla little overwhelmed -
亲爱的，我们都有点不知所措了-
Good point.You're not a war-time Mom.
说得好。你不是战时妈妈。
Why don't you findyour version of Dad,
你为什么不找到你心目中的爸爸，
and take a break,take a holiday.
休息一下，去度假。
I don't have time to wait foryour confirmation,
我没时间等你的确认，
so let's just say,if you're here in 10 minutes,
如果你10分钟后到这里，
I'll have you removed.
我要把你搬走。
And then, the GoTronsmake the GoTrons,
然后，哥德伦人变成了哥德伦人，
make the GoTrons,make the GoTrons.
制造哥特龙，制造哥特龙。
Couple of snags, but I knowhow to speed things up.
有几个障碍，但我知道如何加快速度。
Remember when we talked abouthow the best thing we could do
还记得我们谈过我们能做的最好的事吗
for the family is to recruitoutside the family?
对于家庭来说，是不是要在家庭之外招兵买马？
Yes. Way ahead of you.
对。在你前面。
Summer, I want youto meet Kendra.
Summer，我想让你见见Kendra。
She's froma temp agency.
她是临时工。
She's got an entire workforceready to go,
她已经准备好了所有的工作人员，
and all of them have previousgiant robot pilot experience.
他们都有过巨型机器人飞行员的经验。
So, we'll be ready to goahead of schedule.
所以，我们将准备好提前完成计划。
Well, I don't knowabout that but --
我不知道但是--
Well, Kendra knows. So...
嗯，肯德拉知道。所以。。。
So....
所以。。。。
You hereto break my legs?
你打断了我的腿？
No. We're here to talkshit about your sister,
不，我们是来谈论你妹妹的，
because she justfired us.
因为她刚刚解雇了我们。
-You're kidding.-Arrogant little bitch.
-你开玩笑吧。-傲慢的小婊子。
Should we clip her?No. She's not worth doing time.
我们应该夹住她吗？不，她不值得花时间。
You wouldn't do time.You brought her into the world.
你不会浪费时间。你把她带到了这个世界。
So, I cantake her out.
所以，我可以带她出去。
You thought there wasan actual law?
你以为有真正的法律？
It's a jokemothers say.
别人说这是个玩笑。
What kind of fucked up worldhave you been living in?
你生活在一个什么样的世界？
Uh, one where your mothermurdering you
呃，一个你母亲谋杀你的地方
isn't acomedic premise?
这不是医生的前提吗？
Guys, there's a littleadjustment period,
伙计们，有一段调整期，
but pretty soon, you're gonnato return to normal,
但很快，你就会恢复正常，
and you're not going towant to kill Summer.
你不会想杀了Summer的。
You're not even gonnabe mad at her.
你不会生她的气的。
Nah, fuck her.She's my enemy.
不，操她。她是我的敌人。
Should we kill ourselves, so wecan get to hell before her,
我们应该自杀，这样我们才能在她之前下地狱，
and hide nearthe entrance?
躲在入口附近？
I like that.
我喜欢这样。
Rick fired me.
里克解雇了我。
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉。
Are you okay, baby?What happened to us?
你没事吧，宝贝？我们怎么了？
We lost our minds.
我们失去了理智。
I did it.Morty was right.
我做到了。莫蒂是对的。
I got addictedto making Grandpa happy.
我沉迷于让爷爷开心。
It's only becauseyour Grandpa
只是因为你爷爷
inflates the valueof his happiness.
夸大了他幸福的价值。
That's a good point.I mean, look at me.
这是一个很好的观点。我是说，看看我。
I'm easy to make happy,which is why
我很容易快乐，这就是为什么
nobody gives a shitif I am.
如果我是谁，谁也不在乎。
I appreciate it, but there'ssomething else too.
我很感激，但还有别的事。
I've been really sensitiveabout family lately
我最近对家庭很敏感
because of somethingI've been keeping secret.
因为一些我一直保密的事情。
Okay. Who's onthe Supreme Court,
可以。谁是最高法院的法官，
and what statedo we live in?
我们住在哪个州？
It's been yearssince I've thought about this.
我想这个已经有一年了。
No, I'm not pregnant.
不，我没有怀孕。
But as you guys recall, and as alot of people keep bringing up,
但正如你们所记得的，当很多人不断提起，
Morty and I did accidentallycreate a giant incest baby,
莫蒂和我不小心生了一个巨大的乱伦婴儿，
which the governmentdid launch into space.
是政府发射到太空的。
And I'm not surehow to tell you this,
我不知道该怎么告诉你，
but it is still alive, and Ihave been in contact with it.
但它还活着，我一直在和它接触。
There were soldiers waiting forme outside school last month.
上个月有士兵在学校外面等我。
They took me to the Pentagon,and briefed me.
他们把我带到五角大楼，向我做了简报。
And from there, I was shuttledto a secret base on Mars.
从那里，我被穿梭到火星上的一个秘密基地。
They had captured him,and wanted to see
他们抓住了他，想看看
if he'd respond to me,instinctively, being his mother.
如果他本能地回应我，做他的母亲。
And he sure did.
他确实做到了。
But what they didn't expectwas that I'd respond to him.
但他们没想到的是我会回应他。
I was supposed to helpdiscipline him,
我本应该帮助管教他的，
so they could turn him intothe ultimate weapon.
所以他们可以把他变成终极武器。
Instead, I trained him to love,to believe in himself,
相反，我训练他去爱，去相信自己，
and finally,to escape.
最后，逃走。
The government doesn't wantanyone to know it happened,
政府不想让任何人知道发生了什么，
but it's only a matter of timebefore the story comes out.
但故事出来只是时间问题。
And when it does, all we'regoing to have is each other.
当它发生的时候，我们所要拥有的就是彼此。
And you guys are a couple,and Rick has Morty,
你们是一对，里克有莫蒂，
but I'm the odd one out
但我是个怪人
So, I wanted to make surewe stuck together.
所以，我想确保我们在一起。
But instead, I drove us apart,and Rick replaced me
但是相反，我把我们分开了，里克代替了我
with an anime girl,so all I've got is myself
和一个动漫女孩在一起，所以我只有我自己
and my giant, tortured,government-trained rogue
我的巨人，折磨，政府训练的流氓
incest monster babyout there in space somewhere.
乱伦怪兽宝宝在太空某处。
Oh, baby.What the fuck.
哦，宝贝。他妈的。
And then, you have to wonder,what else are they doingwith our taxes?
然后，你会想，他们还拿我们的税干什么？
Wait. Summer,what did you just say?
等待。Summer，你刚才说什么？
Morty, a lot.
莫蒂，很多。
He replaced you withan anime girl?
他用一个动漫女孩取代了你？
Big eyes?Plus signs for teeth?
大眼睛？牙齿的标志？
Ends sentences with weird soundsthat don't fit?
以奇怪的声音结束句子不合适？
Yeah. That's going to behis whole crew now.
是 啊。这将是全体船员现在。
And they're about to run theirfirst test on the GoGoGoTron.
他们将在Gogotron上进行第一次测试。
Those people wantto steal the robots.
那些人想偷机器人。
Th-they're gonna kill Rick.He's all alone.
他们要杀了瑞克。他一个人。
We-we-we've gotto go save him.
我们得去救他。
Right.Or... you know, fuck him.
对。或者。。。你知道，去他妈的。
I'm good with that.Yeah, fuck him.
我不介意。是的，去他妈的。
Guys, a great leader once toldme you get the family you get.
伙计们，一个伟大的领袖曾经告诉过你，你得到了你的家人。
Rick:Alright. It works. Now, we justgot to find a giant monster.
里克：好的。它起作用了。现在，我们只需要找到一个巨大的怪物。
My sensors havepicked one up, Rick.
我的传感器检测到了一个，瑞克。
Okay. OkayLock onto its location.
可以。好的锁定它的位置。
Yeah, got it.
是的，明白了。
Oh, it's you!
哦，是你！
Huh?
嗯？
What the hell is this?
这到底是什么？
Thanks for makingthe biggest robot ever, Rick.
谢谢你做了史上最大的机器人，瑞克。
We'll take it from here.
我们从这里开始。
You little assholes!
你们这些小混蛋！
You son of a bitch!
你这狗娘养的！
Lock a load, boys.
锁上一堆东西，孩子们。
Say "hello"to my little me.
向我的小我问好。
Give up, old man.The G3 is ours.
放弃吧，老头。G3是我们的。
And last I checked,your "family"
最后我查了一下，你的“家人”
wasn't comingto save you, hmm?
不是来救你的，嗯？
Giant Invest Baby:Go go goo goo.
巨资宝贝：咕咕咕咕。
Holy mother of mercy!
仁慈的圣母！
My God.It's beautiful.
天哪。真漂亮。
Yeah! Family!
是 啊！家人！
-Is that ---It's exactly whatit looks like. Yes.
-这就是它的样子。对。
Congrats, man.I see the resemblance.
恭喜你，伙计。我看到了相似之处。
Form the Energy Sword!Activate the Goddamn sword!
形成能量之剑！启动该死的剑！
Oh, man, the sword. Maybe wedidn't think this through.
哦，天哪，剑。也许我们没想清楚。
They're not actually gonnaattack a space baby, are they?
他们其实不是太空婴儿，是吗？
I never thought I'd bethe one to say this,
我从没想过我会这么说，
but you need to watchmore anime, Mom.
但是你需要看更多的动画，妈妈。
Whoa, easy now,Naruto.
哇，放松点，火影忍者。
Bahbah go bye-bye!
去吧，再见！
Kendra: What the hellis wrong with you people?!
肯德拉：你们到底怎么了？！
You just havean incest space monsterin your back pocket, huh?
你的后口袋里有个乱伦空间怪物？
Welcome tothe Smith family.
欢迎来到史密斯一家。
Shit. Put that down, Naruto.Your great-grandpa is in there.
倒霉。放下枪，火影忍者。你的曾祖父在里面。
What do you say?One last zipline?
你说呢？最后一个拉链？
Incest space baby.Nicely done.
乱伦太空宝贝。干得好。
Morty: After that, things prettymuch went back to normal --
莫蒂：那之后，prettymuch的情况又恢复正常了--
some version of it, anyway.
不管怎样，是它的某个版本。
Rick said GoTrons were lamelittle kid bullshit,
里克说哥德伦是个蹩脚的小子，
and we never talkedabout them again.
我们再也没提起过他们。
Summer:Except all those gigantic spacebugs were still runnin' loose,
Summer:除了那些巨大的太空虫还在逍遥法外，
and there were no GoTrons leftto fight them.
没有哥特伦人能和他们战斗。
Morty: Yeah, millions dieevery day.
莫蒂：是啊，每天都有数百万人死亡。
Summer: But you want to knowwhat they could never kill?
萨默：但你想知道他们永远杀不了什么吗？
Family.
家庭。
-Where's Jerry?-Help!
-杰瑞呢？-救命！
Help! I'm still out here!
救命啊！我还在外面！
Morty: Yep, nothing'smore important than--
莫蒂：是的，没有什么比--
Hey! Hey!Whoa-whoa-whoa!
嘿！嘿！喔，喔，喔！
Ugh!
啊！
And just like that, I knewour goose was as cooked as --
就这样，我知道鹅已经煮好了--
Voiceovarians. Ugh.
语音卵巢。啊。
♪ Magic sights,exciting sounds ♪
♪ 神奇的景象，令人兴奋的声音♪
♪ Come day or night,and feel around ♪
♪ 无论白天黑夜，都要来感受一下♪
♪ This is the worldfor you ♪
♪ 这是你的世界♪
♪ No matter whereyou've ever been ♪
♪ 不管你去过哪里♪
♪ This is the placeyour life begiii-i-ins ♪
♪ 这是你人生的起点♪
♪ Boob World ♪
♪ 胸部世界♪
♪ It's a world for you,but it's actually two ♪
♪ 对你来说这是一个世界，但实际上是两个♪
♪ Boob Wo-o-orld ♪
♪ 胸部世界♪
Samansky,you're late!
萨曼斯基，你迟到了！
Won't happen again, sir!
不会再发生了，先生！
Bugs,. Look to your left.Now, look to your right.
漏洞，。看你的左边。现在，看你的右边。
None of you are coming back.Not one.
你们都不回来了，一个也不回来。
In the entire historyof this program,
在这个项目的整个历史中，
not a single bughas returned.
一个虫子也没有回来。
Alright. Bring it in!
好吧。把它拿进来！
What are we?-Normal-sized bugs!
我们是什么？-正常大小的虫子！
-What do we do?-Travel throughan interdimensional
-我们该怎么办？-穿越多维空间
gateway to a planetwith tiny people!
通往一个小星球的大门！
-Why do we do it?-To spread the cure for AIDS!
-我们为什么要这么做？-传播治疗艾滋病的方法！
Hey, Sarge, how do we know ifthese little people
嘿，中士，我们怎么知道这些小家伙
can understand us?
你能理解我们吗？
I mean, do these evenspeak Buganese?
我是说，这些人会说布加内斯语吗？
Funny, Palicki.That's why we say it very loud.
有趣，帕利基。这就是为什么我们说得很大声。
Guys, you'll still be the samecivilized bug on their side.
伙计们，你们仍然是他们这边的同类。
It's not likeinterdimensional travel
这不像是跨空间旅行
strips us of our clothes,and makes us screaming monsters.
剥去我们的衣服，让我们尖叫的怪物。
Or maybe it does.It's impossible to know.
也许是的。不可能知道。
Now, get out of here!
现在，离开这里！
My clothes --where'd they go?
我的衣服——它们去哪儿了？
Man: Did you get any of that?
男人：你收到了吗？